<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>https://robgoyal.github.io/</id><title>Robin Goyal</title><subtitle>A Mechatronics Engineering graduate from McMaster University, self-taught software developer working for the Government of Canada and interested in all things technology.</subtitle> <updated>2023-03-12T22:49:46-04:00</updated> <author> <name>Robin Goyal</name> <uri>https://robgoyal.github.io/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://robgoyal.github.io/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="https://robgoyal.github.io/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2023 Robin Goyal </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Set up Cloudflare tunnels with Nginx Proxy Manager</title><link href="https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/cloudflare-tunnels-with-npm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Set up Cloudflare tunnels with Nginx Proxy Manager" /><published>2023-03-11T11:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2023-03-11T11:00:00-05:00</updated> <id>https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/cloudflare-tunnels-with-npm/</id> <content src="https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/cloudflare-tunnels-with-npm/" /> <author> <name>Robin Goyal</name> </author> <category term="Homelab" /> <summary> Recently, I learned about Cloudflare tunnels and how you can safely expose your internal services without opening any ports on your router and I was mindblown! In this post, I’ll show how to set up the Cloudflare tunnel, installing Docker services, using a wildcard subdomain to route all requests to NPM (Nginx Proxy Manager), and adding Google authentication to your applications. Why Cloudflar... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Creating my first Linux VM in Proxmox</title><link href="https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/create-vm-proxmox/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Creating my first Linux VM in Proxmox" /><published>2023-03-01T14:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2023-03-01T14:00:00-05:00</updated> <id>https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/create-vm-proxmox/</id> <content src="https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/create-vm-proxmox/" /> <author> <name>Robin Goyal</name> </author> <category term="Homelab" /> <summary> It’s been a few months since I have worked on my home lab but after learning about Cloudflare Tunnels, it has reinvigorated the youth in me to tackle this problem again. Over the next couple of blog posts, I will document my findings about this technology the best that I can. The one caveat being which I mentioned I would do in a previous post is to document how to install Proxmox on baremetal... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Proxmox Backup Server on Raspberry Pi</title><link href="https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/pbs-rpi/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Proxmox Backup Server on Raspberry Pi" /><published>2022-11-13T13:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2023-03-12T21:29:10-04:00</updated> <id>https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/pbs-rpi/</id> <content src="https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/pbs-rpi/" /> <author> <name>Robin Goyal</name> </author> <category term="Homelab" /> <summary> This is my second post in a series of blog posts (in no particular order) to build my homelab. These posts and this homelab will be a living being connected to myself. As I grow and learn more about system administration and networking, so will the homelab. Today’s post will document how to deploy Proxmox Backup Server as a Docker container on the Raspberry Pi. If you haven’t seen my previous ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Configure a Raspberry Pi from scratch</title><link href="https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/configure-raspberry-pi-from-scratch/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Configure a Raspberry Pi from scratch" /><published>2022-11-12T11:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2023-03-12T21:29:10-04:00</updated> <id>https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/configure-raspberry-pi-from-scratch/</id> <content src="https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/configure-raspberry-pi-from-scratch/" /> <author> <name>Robin Goyal</name> </author> <category term="Homelab" /> <summary> Earlier this year, I converted my old desktop into a Proxmox server (you’re probably wondering why I’m talking about Proxmox on a post discussing the Raspberry Pi but we’ll get there) in an effort to offload the work of virtualizing VM’s on my devices. Whether it was a development VM or a Kali VM for my cybersecurity related activities, I was creating and managing VM’s on multiple devices. Sett... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Mr. Robot (Try Hack Me)</title><link href="https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/thm-mrrobot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mr. Robot (Try Hack Me)" /><published>2021-09-20T21:30:00-04:00</published> <updated>2022-01-24T21:23:51-05:00</updated> <id>https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/thm-mrrobot/</id> <content src="https://robgoyal.github.io/posts/thm-mrrobot/" /> <author> <name>Robin Goyal</name> </author> <category term="Cybersecurity" /> <category term="Writeups" /> <summary> I am currently in the process of completing these boxes on Try Hack Me again in an effort to document my experience, reinforce my knowledge of the topics, and improve my ability to concisely communicate the pentest lifecycle. Scenario Title: Mr. Robot Description: Based on the Mr. Robot show, can you root this box? Free/Subscriber: Free Difficulty: Medium Enumeration From the informati... </summary> </entry> </feed>
